ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Files /4283/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Lead Safety, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 09C#3528, 11/10/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 09C#3529, 11/24/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 09C#3530, 12/08/09, Brown
- Dust for California Farmworkers, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  #3531
- HOSPIRA, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  WNYCOSH, #3532, 12/12/08
- GBEC, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  WNYCOSH, #3533, 03/24/09
- Confined Space, Hazards in Agriculture, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  WNYCOSH, #3534, 03/19/09
- Respiratory Protection- MCWA (at WTP), 2008 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  WNYCOSH, #3535, 12/16/08
- Female Firefighter Conference, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  Int'l Association of Women in Fire Emergency Services, #3536, 05/15/09
- Mandatory Overtime, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  CSEA, #3537, 01/08/09
- Erie 1 Boces- Tech. Asst.- Fungi, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH, #3538, 12/12/08
- Sexual Harassment, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  WNYCOSH, #3539, 12/29/08
- Lead Supervisor Contractor Refresher, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  Chautauqua Home Rehab., 08C#3540, 1/15/09, Brown
- Lead Worker Refresher, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  Chautauqua Home Rehab, 08C#3541, 1/16/09, Brown
- City of N.F., 2009 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  WNYCOSH, #3543, 04/30/09
- City of N.F., 2009 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  WNYCOSH, #3545, 08/09
- Hilton School District- Art Supplies, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  WNYCOSH, #3546, 06/26/09
- Green Cling- Erie 1 Boces, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  WNYCOSH, #3547, 11/30/09
- No. 3548: AFL-CIO, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Gates-Chili School District, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  WNYCOSH, #3549, 10/09
- Gates-Chili School District, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  WNYCOSH, #3550, 10/09/09
- Gates-Chili School District, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  WNYCOSH, #3551, 10/09/09
- NYS Cosmetology Association Conference, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  WNYCOSH, #3553, 06/08/09, Brown
- Broome County (Proposal), 2009 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  #3554
- Boilermakers, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  WNYCOSH, #3555, 02/13/09
- NYSTA, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  WNYCOSH, #3556, 04/21/09
- Breast Cancer and Environmental Awareness, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  #3557, FSWNYS
- MD/HRM, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  #3558
- Methanol Training (Proposed), 2009 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  O'Brien and Gere, #3560
- #3561, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  03/02/09
- Lead R.A.R., 2009 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  NYC Dept of Health- MH, #3563, 04/17/09
- Lead Insp.- I, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  NYC Dept. of Health, #3564
- Dig. Protocol, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  MSU, #3566
- Workplace Violence, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  HRATT, #3567, 06/17/10
- Rochester Community Health Clinic, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  WNYCOSH, #3568, 07/17/09
- NYSUT (Proposed), 2009 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  #3569
- USCC, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  #3570, 01/24/10
- Tech. Asst., On Firefighters, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  Taldone, esq., #3571, 04/29/09
- Chautauqua County DPH (Proposed), 2009 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  #3576
- OMROD (Proposed), 2009 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  #3572
- No. 3573: Lead Abatement Worker [Folder 1 of 2], 2010 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  Contains SSN's
- No. 3573: Lead Abatement Worker [Folder 2 of 2], 2010 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- NYS Pollution Prevention Grant, 2008-2009 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  #3573
- NYSDOL HAB, 2009-2010 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, #3573
- Lead Worker, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  MCDPH, #3573,
- Urban Community Corp, 2008-2010 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  W/ SUNY AB, ECC, WNYCOSH, #3573
- Safe Patient Handling and Green Projects, 2009-2010 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  WNYCOSH (NYS Legislative Initiative), #3573
- Vulnerable Workers (OSHA Grant), 2009-2010 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- No. 3574: Monroe County Lead Abatement [Folder 1 of 3], 2009-2011 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- No. 3574: Monroe County Lead Abatement [Folder 2 of 3], 2009-2011 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- No. 3574: Monroe County Lead Abatement [Folder 3 of 3], 2009-2011 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Cornell Labor Programs, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  #3575, 09/09/09
- Safety and Health Committees, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  WNYCOSH, #3579, 07/07/09
- Safety and Health Committees, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  WNYCOSH, #3580, 09/23/09
- Safety and Health Committees, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  WNYCOSH, #3581, 11/12/09
- Mold, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  WNYCOSH, #3582, 08/05/09
- Mold, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  WNYCOSH, #3583, 10/14/09
- Mold, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  WNYCOSH, #3584, 01/19/10
- JHA Vet. School, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  BCERF, #3585, 08/12-13/09
- JHA, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  BCERF, #3586
- Chemicals, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH, #3588, 08/05/09
- Chemicals, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  WNYCOSH, #3589, 10/17/09
- Chemicals, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  WNYCOSH, #3590, 01/19/10
- Training Skills, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  WNYCOSH, #3591, 09/21-22/09
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  WNYCOSH, #3592, 08/26/09
- Lead Safe Work Practices Trainer, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  WNYCOSH, #3593, 08/27/09
- Lead Worker- I, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  WNYCOSH, #3594, 04/28-29/10
- ERGO, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  WNYCOSH, #3595, 09/30/09
- ERGO, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  WNYCOSH, #3596, 11/30/09
- ERGO, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  WNYCOSH, #3597, 01/29/10
- Pandemic Planning (Proposed), 2009 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  1st Niagara Bank, #3598
- NEPH Conference, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  #3599
- Children's Book About Dangerous Jobs (Proposed), 2009 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  #3600
- Tech. Asst., 2009 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  NYSDEC, #3601, 06/19/09
- Tech. Asst., Mold, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  Markowitz, #3602, 9/11/07
- On- Farm Training, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  WNYCOSH, #3603, 10/27/09
- Hazcom, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  WNYCOSH, #3604, 12/08/09
- PPE, Respiratory Protection, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  #3605
- Biohazards and Violence, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  NYWEA, #3606, 07/08/10
- Conference Workshop, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  USCC, #3607, 01/25/10
- Conference (Proposed), 2011 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  Int'l Association of Women in Fire Emergency Services, #3608, 08/11
- Conference Module, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  NYSWPFF's, #3609, 09/29/09
- N.F.- W.V., 2009 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  WNYCOSH, #3610, 11/16/09
- N.F.- W.V., 2009 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  WNYCOSH, #3611, 11/16/09
- N.F.- W.V., 2009 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  WNYCOSH, #3612, 11/18/09
- N.F.- W.V., 2009 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  WNYCOSH, #3613, 11/18/09
- N.F.- W.V., 2009 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  WNYCOSH, #3614, 11/20/09
- N.F.- W.V., 2009 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  WNYCOSH, #3615, 11/20/09
- N.F.- W.V., 2009 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  WNYCOSH, #3616, 12/01/09
- N.F.- W.V., 2009 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  WNYCOSH, #3617, 12/01/09
- N.F.- W.V., 2009 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  WNYCOSH, #3618, 12/10/09
- N.F.- W.V., 2009 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, #3619, 12/10/09
- Chemical Hazards- Little Falls, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, #3622, 10/20/09
- Chemical Hazards- Fishkill, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  WNYCOSH, #3623, 10/21/09
- Chemical Hazards- Bergen Pt., 2009 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  NYWEA, #3624, 10/22/09
- Conference, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  NYWEA, #3627, 02/03/10
- Podcast, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  BCERF, #3628 (2860), 08/19/09
- Tech. Asst., 2009 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  NYSDUG, #3629, 08/19/09
- No. 3630: NYSUT [Folder 1 of 7], 2009-2014 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- No. 3630: NYSUT [Folder 2 of 7], 2009-2014 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- No. 3630: NYSUT [Folder 3 of 7], 2009-2014 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- No. 3630: NYSUT [Folder 4 of 7], 2009-2014 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- No. 3630: NYSUT [Folder 5 of 7], 2009-2014 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- No. 3630: NYSUT [Folder 6 of 7], 2009-2014 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- No. 3630: NYSUT [Folder 7 of 7], 2009-2014 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Indoor Air Quality/USEPA RFP (Proposed), 2009 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  WNYCOSH, #3631
- MCWA, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  WNYCOSH, #3632, 10/07/09
- MCWA, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  WNYCOSH, #3633, 11/04/09
- Coke Oven Emissions, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  Clean Air Coalition, #3634, 03/17/10
- Lead Safe Work Practices Exams, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH, #3635
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  WNYCOSH, #3635, 04/26/10
- Buffalo-Ed, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  WNYCOSH, #3636, 10/13/09
- Buffalo-Ed, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  WNYCOSH, #3637, 10/15/09
- Buffalo-Ed, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  WNYCOSH, #3638, 10/15/09
- Buffalo-Ed, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  WNYCOSH, #3640, 10/28/09
- Buffalo-Ed, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  WNYCOSH, #3641, 10/29/09
- Buffalo-Ed, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  WNYCOSH, #3642, 10/29/09
- Buffalo-Ed, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  WNYCOSH, #3643, 10/30/09
- Buffalo-Ed, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  WNYCOSH, #3644, 11/02/09
- Buffalo-Ed, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  WNYCOSH, #3645, 11/05/09
- Buffalo-Ed, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  WNYCOSH, #3646, 11/05/09
- Buffalo-Ed, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  WNYCOSH, #3647, 11/06/09
- Lead Training (Proposed), 2009 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  WNYCOSH, #3648
- Rapid Interviews, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  WHCU, #3649-3650, 09/17-18/09
- Workplace Violence, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  Mary Catt, #3651, 9/09
- APWA Conference, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  WNYCOSH, #3652, 04/08/10
- Hazmat-I, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  IUOE, #3653, 01/28/10
- Hazmat Refresher, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  IUOE, #3654, 03/03/10
- Hazmat Refresher, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  IUOE, #3655, 03/04/10
- Hazmat Refresher, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  IUOE, #3656, 03/05/10
- Hazmat Refresher, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  IUOE, #3657, 03/08/10
- Hazmat Refresher, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  IUOE, #3658, 03/09/10
- Hazmat Initial, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  IUOE, #3659, 02/04/10
- Hazmat Refresher [Folders 1-11], 2010 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  IUOE, #3660-3670, 02/20/10-03/13/10
- Hazmat Initial, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  IUOE, #3671, 01/12/10
- Hazmat Initial, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  IUOE, #3672, 02/09/10
- Hazop, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  WNYCOSH, #3673, 01/13/10
- Hazop, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  WNYCOSH, #3674, 01/20/10
- Trainer, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  WNYCOSH, #3675, 01/14-15/10
- E.D. and H.N., 2009 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  WNYCOSH, #3676, 12/03/09
- E.D. and H.N., 2009 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  WNYCOSH, #3677, 12/08/09
- E.D. and H.N., 2009 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  WNYCOSH, #3678, 12/15/09
- Hazop, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  WNYCOSH, #3679, 06/02/10
- Hazop, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  WNYCOSH, #3680, 06/04/10
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  WNYCOSH, 10C#3681, 7/24/10, Wheaton
- MCWA, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  WNYCOSH, #3682, 12/09/09
- MCWA, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, #3683, 12/11/09
- #3685, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  10/7/09
- Tech. Asst., 2009 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  #3686, 10/13/09
- AFL-CIO Central Labor Council, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  WNYCOSH, #3687, 11/10/09
- ERGO: Vulnerable Workers, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  WNYCOSH, #3688, 11/12/09
- UFCW (Syracuse), 2010 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH, #3689, 04/13/10
- UFCW (Buffalo), 2010 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  WNYCOSH, #3690, 04/14/10
- Indoor Air Quality Investigation, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  Ciminelli, #3691, 11/13/09
- Work, Health, and Health Care, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  Cornell ILR, #3692, 02/16/10
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  Public, 09C#3693, 12/09/09, Brown
- Fire Station Living Conditions, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  #3694
- H1N1 Report, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  #3695
- Tech. Asst., 2010 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  Hospira, #3696, 02/10
- Lead RR and P (Proposal), 2010 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  Onondaga County, #3697
- Buffalo 200- Confined Space, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  WNYCOSH, #3698, 06/29/10
- Buffalo 200- Hazcom, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  WNYCOSH, #3699, 06/22/10
- Buffalo 200- Hazcom, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  WNYCOSH, #3700, 05/13/10
- Buffalo 200- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  WNYCOSH, #3701, 06/01/10
- Buffalo Zoo- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH, #3702, 06/03/10
- Lead Training (Proposal), 2010 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  County of Rochester, #3703
- Aging Workforce, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  WNYCOSH, #3704, 02/03/10
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3705, 1/19/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator Refresher, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3706, 1/20/10, Brown
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3707, 2/16/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator Refresher, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3708, 2/17/10, Brown
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3709, 3/9/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator Refresher, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3710, 3/10/10, Brown
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3711, 4/6/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator Refresher, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3712, 4/7/10, Brown
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3713, 5/4/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator Refresher, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3714, 5/5/10, Brown
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3715, 6/7/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator Refresher, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3716, 6/8/10, Brown
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3717, 7/20/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator Refresher, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3718, 7/21/10, Brown
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3719, 8/10/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator Refresher, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3720, 8/11/10, Brown
- No. 3721: Monroe County Lead Safe Work Practices [Folder 1 of 2], 2008-2010 (Box 28, Folder 40)
- No. 3721: Monroe County Lead Safe Work Practices [Folder 2 of 2], 2008-2010 (Box 28, Folder 41)
- Lead Renovator Refresher, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3722, 9/15/10, Brown
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3723, 10/5/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator Refresher, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3724, 10/6/10, Brown
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3725, 11/9/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator Refresher, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3726. 11/10/10, Brown
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3727, 12/7/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator Refresher, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3728, 12/8/10, Brown
- No. 3729: Safe Patient Handling Teams [Folder 1 of 3], 2010 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- No. 3729: Safe Patient Handling Teams [Folder 2 of 3], 2010 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- No. 3729: Safe Patient Handling Teams [Folder 3 of 3], 2010 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- No. 3730: Monroe County Lead Abatement Worker Program, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Hazcom, Ergo, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  WNYCOSH, #3731, 05/18/10
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  Public Program, 10C#3732, 1/14/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator Refresher, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  Public Program, 10C#3734, 1/28/10, Brown
- NYWEA, Biohazards and Violence, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  WNYCOSH, #3735, 5/5/10
- Conference, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  USCC, #3736, 1/25/11
- Biohazards and Violence, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  NYWEA, #3737, 5/27/10
- Confined Space, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  NYWEA, #3738, 7/1/10
- Confined Space, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  NYWEA, #3739, 8/11/10
- Fishkill, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  NYWEA, #3740, 08/12/10
- #3741 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  Public Program, 10C#3742, 2/1/10, Brown
- Shiftwork, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  Civil Service Employees Association, #3743, 4/30/10
- MI/ Health and Safety, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  WNYCOSH, #3744, 4/12/10
- Tech. Asst., 2010 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  Tonawanda Coke Corp., #3745, 2/5/10
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  Public Program, 10C#3746, 2/25/10, Balfour/Brown
- Critters, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  CSEA, #3747, 04/30/10
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  WNYCOSH, #3748, 04/27/10
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  WNYCOSH, 10C#3749, 3/11/10, Balfour
- LRRP-R, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  WNYCOSH, #3750, 5/6/10
- LRRP-R, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  WNYCOSH, #3751, 5/7/10
- Mold, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  WNYCOSH, #3752, 3/16/10
- Chemical Safety, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  WNYCOSH, #3753, 3/16/10
- Safer and "Greener" Guide, 2009-2010 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  WNYCOSH, #3754, 8/9 - 7/10
- Indoor Air Quality, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  Tools for Schools, #3755
- Office Safety- Alfred State University, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  WNYCOSH, #3758, 7/8/10
- Blood Borne Pathogens- Alfred State University, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  WNYCOSH, #3757, 7/7/10
- Blood Borne Pathogens- Alfred State University, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  WNYCOSH, #3759, 6/8/10
- Hazard Analysis Workshop (HAWP), 2010 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  WNYCOSH, #3760, 04/20/10
- Hazop, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  WNYCOSH, #3761, 4/20/10
- Confined Space, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  WNYCOSH, #3762, 5/17/10
- Confined Space, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  WNYCOSH, #3763, 5/21/10
- Confined Space, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  WNYCOSH, #3764, 05/27/10
- Wyoming County Correctional Facility, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, #3765, 4/21/10
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  Public, 10C#3766, 3/25/10, Balfour/Brown
- Lead Renovator- Refresher, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  Public, 10C#3767, 3/26/10, Balfour/Brown
- Ergonomics, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  WNYCOSH, #3768, 05/14/10
- Ergonomics, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  WNYCOSH, #3769, 5/14/10
- Tech. Asst., 2010 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  Buffalo Public Schools, #3770, 3/29/10
- Composting Health and Safety, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  USCC, #3771, 8/6/10
- Tech. Asst., 2010 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  Cornell EDI, #3773
- Violence- Racker Center, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  WNYCOSH, #3774, 5/24/10
- MCWA- Hazcom, PPE, Respiratory Protection, Hearing Protection, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  WNYCOSH, #3778, 5/20/10
- Lead Safe Work Practice, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3780, 5/11/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator Refresher, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3781, 5/18/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator Refresher, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3782, 5/12/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator- Refresher, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3783, 7/8/10, Brown
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3784, 6/21/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator- Refresher, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3785, 6/22/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator- Refresher, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3786, 6/22/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator- Refresher, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3787, 7/21/10, Brown
- Lead Safe Work Practice, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3788, 7/27/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator- Refresher, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3789, 7/28/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator- Refresher, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3790, 7/28/10, Brown
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3791, 8/24/10, Balfour
- Lead Renovator- Refresher, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3792, 8/11/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator- Refresher, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3793, 8/25/10
- Lead Renovator- Refresher, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3794, 8/25/10, Balfour
- Lead Safe Work Practice, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3795, 9/28/10, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Refresher, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3796, 9/15/10, Brown
- Lead Renovator- Refresher, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3797, 9/29/10, Balfour
- Lead Renovator- Refresher, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3798, 9/29/10, Balfour
- Mold, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  WNYCOSH, #3799, 7/6/10
- Chemical Safety, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  WNYCOSH, #3800, 7/6/10
- Buffalo Firefighters, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  #3801, 5/12/10
- Article- Breast Cancer- Female Firefighters, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  NIST.Gov, #3802, 05/2010
- Eberl v. FMC, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  P.W. Beltz, #3803, 5/19/10
- Safety and Health Committee Skills, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  WNYCOSH, #3804, 7/26/10
- Workplace Violence (Proposed), 2010 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  Chemung A.R.C., #3805
- OHM- Boces- Green Cling., 2010 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  WNYCOSH, #3806, 7/27/10
- Confined Space- Onondaga County, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  WNYCOSH, #3807, 7/28/10
- Confined Space- Onondaga County, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  WNYCOSH, #3808, 7/29/10
- Review Article, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  e-Extension Farm Energy Website, #3809, 6/23/10
- Article/Interview, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  INC. Magazine, #3811, 5/10/10
- Manure safety, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  #3812
- Tech. Asst., 2010 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  QUIMBY, #3813, 6/4/10
- Tech. Asst., 2010 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  Ciminelli, #3814, 6/30/10
- MCWA, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  WNYCOSH, #3815, 9/15/10
- Welding- MCWA, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  WNYCOSH, #3816, 09/15/10
- Hazcom/Noise/PPE- MCWA, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  WNYCOSH, #3817, 9/2/10
- Welding- MCWA, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 50)
  WNYCOSH, #3818, 9/2/10
- MCWA- Hazcom/PPE, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 51)
  WNYCOSH, #3819, 9/16/10
- MCWA- Hazcom/PPE, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 52)
  WNYCOSH, #3820, 9/29/10
- NYSDOL HAB, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 53)
- MCWA- Hazcom/PPE etc., 2011 (Box 30, Folder 54)
  WNYCOSH, #3821, 5/27/11
- MCWA, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 55)
  WNYCOSH, #3822, 6/8/11
- MCWA, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 56)
  WNYCOSH, #3823, 6/24/11
- Chemung Co., 2010 (Box 30, Folder 57)
  WNYCOSH, #3824, 9/20/10
- Chemung Co., 2010 (Box 30, Folder 58)
  WNYCOSH, #3825, 09/20/10
- MCWA- Office, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 59)
  WNYCOSH, #3826, 09/16/10
- Digester- Boxler Farm, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 60)
  WNYCOSH, 11/02/10, #3827
- Farm Digester Training, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 61)
  WNYCOSH, #3828, 11/04/10
- NYS Cosmetology Association, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 62)
  WNYCOSH, #3829, 9/27/10
- NYS Cosmetology Association, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  WNYCOSH, #3830, 10/25/10
- NWEA- Confined Space at Onondaga County WWTP, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  WNYCOSH, #3831, 6/23/11
- NYWEA- Crisis Management, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, #3832, 12/1/10
- NYWEA- Crisis Management (Binghamton), 2011 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, #3833
- NYWEA- Crisis Management (Fishkill), 2011 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  WNYCOSH, #3834, 6/30/11
- Pandemic Crisis Planning, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  #3835
- Work-Relatedness, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  Cornell ILR, #3836, 10/13/10
- Work-Relatedness, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  Cornell ILR, #3837, 10/13/10
- Occupational Chemical Fundamentals, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  WNYCOSH, #3838, 11/9/10
- Training Skills- Erie County, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  WNYCOSH, #3839, 1/20/11
- Blood Borne Pathogens/Confined Space/Ergonomics- Erie County, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  WNYCOSH, #3840, 10/05/10
- Blood Borne Pathogens/Confined Space/Ergonomics- Erie County, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  WNYCOSH, #3841, 10/7/10